http://www.ivoryclassics.com/privacy/

The Ivory Classics Online Privacy Policy
This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information about your shopping experience. Please see the Yahoo! Privacy Policy for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information.
The Ivory Classics Online Privacy Policy
Ivory Classics is committed to maintaining your confidence and trust, and accordingly maintains the following privacy policy to protect personal information you provide online.
Basic Confidentiality Policy
It is Ivory Classics' policy that personal information, such as your name and e-mail address is private and confidential. Accordingly, the personal information you provide is stored in a secure location, is accessible only by designated staff, and is used only for the purposes for which you provide the information (such as to respond to your inquiries) and to compile an Ivory Classics customer mailing list.
No Release of Information to Third Parties
Personal information will not be released to third parties except to further the purpose for which you provide the information, (such as to respond to your inquiries) or if release is required by law or is pertinent to judicial or governmental investigations or proceedings. There are no other circumstances under which we will provide or sell personal information to third parties.
Page Top
Home
| Ivory Classics Foundation
| Privacy Policy
| Contact
| Help
| Earl Wild Website
© 1998-2006 Ivory Classics. All rights reserved.
xhtml 1.1
| css
| powered by nk113.com
